gamenet.com 2017-12-28

# Geekbeach and Gamenet Privacy Policy

**_GEEKBEACH AND GAMENET PRIVACY POLICY_**

IMPORTANT: By submitting personal data to us you agree that it may be processed by us in the manner described below.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us at **info@gamenet.com**.

GAMENET LIMITED and GEEK BEACH ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy whilst providing an educational and enjoyable gaming experience. We do not target our website or our games to under 13 year olds, but do take measures to help protect those that use our site who are under 13. For example, we do not retain personal information or permit to register those who are known to us to be under 13.

**_Introduction to Privacy Policy_**

This Privacy Policy describes our current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by us from you. The term"Personal Data" refers to information about you personally that you may be asked to submit (e.g. name and email address).

As a result of changes in the law and technology, our data practices will change from time to time. When this happens we will post the changes on our website to notify you of the changes as soon as practicable. We encourage you to check this page frequently.

We will always deal with your Personal Data fairly and in accordance with your instructions. We remind you that this Policy does not apply to third party links beyond this website.

**_Use of Personal Data_**

We will always abide by the Data Protection Act 1998. When we ask you for Personal Data, we tell you the purposes for which we will process that data. These purposes include the following:

\- To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

\- We may contact you to inform you of new services we will be providing, or events or information we think will be of interest to you.

\- We may use your Personal Data for marketing messages from either us or specially selected partners and market research.

\- We may use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our services and to help resolve any problems.

\- By using our service, you agree to allow your username, gameplay and challenge data to be displayed to other users.

**_Opt-out choice_**

If now or at any time in the future you decide that you do not wish to receive information from either us or our partners or you wish to contact our data protection officer, please e-mail us at **info@gamenet.com**.

**_Cookies_**

A "cookie" is a small amount of information that is placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit a website. It collects details of visitor behaviour, which can be used to improve the service delivered to you on a website.

When you visit this site, your Personal Data may be collected using "cookies". Such information is subject to data protection laws and is dealt with in accordance with this Policy. For more information please visit: http://www.aboutcookies.org.

Your computer can be set to accept or reject cookies if you visit the "help" menu on your web browser. However, by rejecting cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of this site's features.

**_Data storage_**

In order for our site and games to function correctly, we may place a small amount of data on your computer or device when you play our games or access our service. It collects hardware and software data and details of visitor behaviour, which can be used to improve the service delivered to you or inform you of new games or services we think may be of interest to you.

If you register with us or if you continue to use our service, you agree to our use of cookies and data storage.

**_Where we store your personal data_**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**_Data Integrity and Security_**

We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of Personal Data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases. Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology.

Any information you provide to us will only be used by us. However, your information may be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectional content on or to this site, or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour towards the site, we may use whatever information we hold to stop such behaviour.

We will hold your Personal Data within our systems for no longer than is reasonably necessary. We will ensure that all your Personal Data is held securely.

The employees who have access to Personal Data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we take all reasonable steps to prevent this from happening.

Your data may be transferred to a third party if Gamenet Limited of Geek Beach or substantially all of its assets are acquired by that third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

**_Data Access and Corrections_**

Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to permit us to identify your Personal Data, we will disclose to you the Personal Data we hold about you. We will also correct, amend or delete any Personal Data that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes.

If you wish to access or correct your Personal Data or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please write to our data protection officer at Market House, 2 Marlborough Road, Swindon, SN3 1QY or e-mail us at **info@gamenet.com**. We do not charge for complying with a correction request, however, for requests for Personal Data, we may charge a small fee to cover our costs.
